From 1887 in Toronto, Manual Life
Financial has expanded its footprints
all over Asia to Indonesia.
[Music]
From
100 to over 1,800 staff and 10,000
agents,
we help customers make financial
decisions by providing key financial
solutions and services.
[Music]
as the world evolves.
Many life evolves with you.
Our growing professional agents, our
marketing offices in 24 cities, our
expanding distribution partners,
our dedicated telearketing team,
our professional and talented staff,
our leading employee benefit and group
life health business are ready to give
the highest quality services and answer
the needs of the Indonesian community.
We are a strong, reliable, trustworthy
and forwardthinking company
proven by hundreds of distinguished
awards and recognitions.
[Music]
As we grow our business, we also of our
community to grow.
Since 1985, we have been serving
millions of customers in Indonesia. Our
diverse international operations
combined with longtime experience in
Indonesia allow us to provide the
expertise to create better product
solutions for Indonesian customers.
[Music]
Manu Life Financial for your future.